> > 布莱恩: 让我给你展示一些非常有用的东西。
&gt;&gt; Brian: So let me show you
something else that's really useful.
如果你把它悬浮在这样的东西上
If you just hover over
something like this,
它会给你函数的定义
it'll give you the function definition.
但是如果你真的是 Cmd+click on the ，它会把你纳入到类型定义中
But if you actually Cmd+click on it, it's
gonna take you into the type definition so
你可以看到这里有什么
you can see exactly what's in here.
>> 布莱恩: 这让你回来了， >> Brian: A S 和
&gt;&gt; Brian: So this gives you back,
&gt;&gt; Brian: A S and
分派<SetState。
Dispatch&lt;SetState.
所以它实际上没有它所做的具体类型。
So it actually doesn't have
a specific type of what it does.
好吧那就好
Okay, that's good to know.
> > 布莱恩: 是的，同样的事。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Yep, same thing.
所以我在这里看的是这里的结肠
So what I'm looking at here
is after this colon here,
我想看看钩子是否有特定的类型
I was trying to see if hooks had
a specific type they returned.
它会告诉你，不，它会返回一个数组。
And it just tells you,
no, it returns an array.
所以我们只需要输入这个
So we just have to type that.
> > 布莱恩: 这还不太正确。
&gt;&gt; Brian: So
this isn't quite correct, yet.
我们所希望的是，这个 createContext，即将成为
What we want this to be is,
this createContext, is going to be, and
我们会给它一个叫做类型参数的东西
we're going to give it what's
here called a type parameter.
这将会是一个弦
And it's gonna be a string.
>> Brian: 字符串和 a的数组， >> Brian: 主题: 字符串，
&gt;&gt; Brian: Array of string and a,
&gt;&gt; Brian: Theme: string,
而这回你的空虚
and this returns to you, void.
所以它不会再回来了好吗
So it doesn't return anything, okay?
> > 布莱恩: 另一件我们忘了的事情。
&gt;&gt; Brian: The other thing we forgot to.
我们必须将 ThemeContext 重命名为 .tsx。
We have to rename ThemeContext to be .tsx.
>> Brian: 您也要命名此 .ts cuz ，其中没有任何 JSX ，但是
&gt;&gt; Brian: You also gotta name this .ts
cuz there's not any JSX in it, but
我把这里的所有东西都重命名了
I just rename everything
TSX at this point, so.
> > 布莱恩: 好的，这就是我们要做的。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay, and
that's all we have to do for this.
这是在告诉 createContext
What this is doing is this
is telling createContext
我们会给它什么东西对吧
what kind of thing we're gonna give it,
right?
我们告诉过我们要给你一个字符串对吧
And we told it we're gonna
give you a string, right?
我们会给你一个以一个字符串和一个
And we're gonna give you a function
that takes in a string and
什么都没做对吧
doesn't give back anything, right?
这就是现在的情况
Which is what this is.
有道理吗
Make sense?
它就像一个类型的参数。
It's like a parameter to a type.
>> 演讲者 2: 不是这样的
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: It's not like that